NICOLAS VAZQUEZ

DEVELOPER .NET

I have worked on various projects as a QA Manual/Automation and used various technologies, as well as developing my own projects in C# and the .NET platform. I consider myself someone with high learning abilities, good memory, logical thinking, patience, personal discipline, great curiosity, creativity, and a strong desire for self-improvement.



_+54 261 247 0389





nicolasvazquezzzz@gmail.com

Achievements

- · Created a landing page, obtained free hosting, completed the project in 3 days, and also generated revenue
- Identified and proposed a solution to optimize the fruit collection process, showcasing problemsolving skills
- Conducted tests, ensured data accuracy, and provided ongoing support for frontend development

Education

Quark Academy

Video Game Developer Course 3 months - present

Egg Academy

Full Stack Developer Course 9 months

QArmy Academy

QA Analyst Course 6 months

You and me institute

English Course 3 years

Hobbies

I am passionate about music, I am a multi-instrumentalist musician and composer 🎵 I also love video games, science, and Stoic philosophy.

Experiencia

2023 - Hoy

Forjadores web | Desarrollador

Marketing agency and e-commerce and single-page web development

2022 - 2023

Holos technology | QA

Testing VR simulators for training in high-risk jobs in the oil and mining industry

2021 - 2022

Quinto impacto | QA

Testing web and mobile applications related to logistical systems and law firm management

2020 - 2021

QArmy | QA

Testing applications for condominium management purposes

Skills

- C# | dotnet
- HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | JavaScript
- Selenium | Playwright
- Git y GitHub
- MySQL | Entity framework
- Postman
- Prompt Engineer

Projectos

Agrolo | Stack: dotnet, entity framework, flutter

Mobile app for managing worker data in the context of a field during harvest season

Role: idea, design, planning, backend, team formation,

testing

Cannon | Stack: Unity, C#

A simple video game where you control a truck that shoots at barrelshaped targets

Role: idea, design, implementation, music composition

Languages

- Fluent English speaker
- Native Spanish speaker